all right
seems since i didn't get someone else to
say they're going to the intro it's on
me uh we're
having our board meeting what number is
this number 14.
number one and number infinity both at
the same time
so uh as stated right before we went
live
there is nothing officially on the
agenda at the moment
uh my assumption is just how do we get
more involvement or how do we create
something that is
more beneficial for our projects if
we're the ones who are we're showing up
and tomorrow is our first
2 p.m one and there should be someone
watching because i'm watching on my
other device
this video is starting soon
full transparency
so yeah what is water is it that would
bring
more value to us in our projects
including just continuing on
as we are doing and also carrie now that
we are live
i would love to hear the update that you
were about to give that i wanted to
see okay okay oh that's awful
um right so so basically
basically i forgot to change the the
namesaver's over
so i couldn't upload the the website so
but it's uploaded but i just can't get
access to it until the namesavers
changed
so complete dick so um i just wanted to
know
about so like contents and that because
they're on
on drupal that there's a kind of book
module
that you can have so whatever content
you can have you can have it like
a book so um i was thinking about
as i said i'm going to create a sandbox
so you can all play in
and i'll set um a few things up on that
and then you can tell me
what you like what you don't like what
you think maybe should be added
so um but there's a book module that
would actually give you so say like if
you had the project
you could have that and you could have
the boot module and you could
put links to different pages where you
could just go in and put stuff
so if people come across it they can
read it like a book and the navigation's
like a book
so i just thought that might be an
interesting way of you know rather than
just having trying to get forums set up
but like if you've got specific project
details like we can we could use the
forums enough for
for research purposes for projects um
because i think it would be too early
for a group also i was speaking to
yvette
yesterday and she's working with we the
whale foundation who's also gonna get um
i think they're live streaming channels
so i think she's gonna get a channel for
that as well
also she's working on a film festival
project
so i've asked her does she want to join
the
the back end of the stuff and then join
us all
and then she can get a a team of people
in with a you know what i mean so they
can so
um everything will be open on the back
end but the project listing
site and the events and that and um is
there anything else that you think that
you might like
um in terms of you know what you would
like
as a sort of like a gang gut sort of
thing
like i know their listing's going to be
on the outside so anyone anonymous
cannot
can see it but if people want to get
more involved with people on the
projects they can come behind the scenes
then so
i've got to kind of structure it so
anonymous people can see it
um and then obviously if they want to
join or leave comments that i'll i'll do
them a special membership
but i said if you want to get involved
either bring their own projects because
i think if
if someone's got an idea for something
like mark did and then put in various
posts and then we can link up
to all the discussion in the various
areas because i know everybody's all
over the place
and discord and and i haven't um
i haven't been in there yet so i don't
know how to forget this setup
then i can sprout out everywhere and
then see what's going on there and then
because
what what i'm doing won't be in facebook
it'll be outside of facebook so people
who are
not interested in being part of facebook
can join as well
you know i mean but we can have links to
all the other sites and you can get
um third-party logins but i don't know
whether you'd want to use your facebook
login to log into the site because
that's possible as well
so if there's anything you can think of
that would be useful
that we don't have just now um if you
can let me know that
is there a downside to having
facebook and google login beyond the
individual one
right that they then have my information
titled i don't know but like obviously
it's you know like if you've got
passwords all over the place
then it's kind of like that but if you
just want to
log in with it so it's easier for you
you know quite happy to do
i use that all the time when it's
available for that very reason that it's
just easier to
have it but if people are looking for
another place to have a conversation
that isn't facebook
one of the other places they go is
discord which does not have the facebook
and google login which is part of the
downfall of it is that you can have
multiple like
every time you click it it creates you a
new account if you don't know how to do
that because if it
links your facebook account but it would
know that you already exist but um
i vote for yes to that but i'm not the
tech person i wouldn't
i wouldn't it's not a big enough barrier
to me when i get there in fact it's a
plus not a minus but it would be a minus
for our
people is my question of the more techy
people that are present
i think as long as it's optional that's
fine
that's most of the facebook and google
logins i've seen you can do the normal
login or you can choose to do facebook
and google
i don't do those um but
i assume people are okay at navigating
that like i
in my experience that the less techy
people who might have confusion finding
the non-fit facebook and google
i think they're more likely to use
facebook and google for logins
and then techy people that or i assume
less likely
should be a bit better at navigating it
but interested to hear what others think
yeah as long as it's optional i should
be fine
yeah that was i didn't know if there
were alternative consequences
that like a non-techie wouldn't see and
be like yes i want to be able to log
in but it's giving facebook and google
our power i mean
every once in a while when someone comes
you forget which one you you used and if
you're using
i can barely hear you the
the same for everyone else does that
look better
no yeah
the audio it auto-adjusted um
the only thing is sometimes people
forget which one they logged in with
but that's not a technical issue it's a
human issue
okay so any other content types
maybe would it help if we had a
discussion on like what we're
doing in that back end like it's it's so
that when someone finds a project they
can come and be part of multiple
projects right
um like i don't know if we envisioned
something for you or that would be way
too complex to make
or whether that would like whether that
would help or hurt you
is is the question no
no be all right because as i said i can
do most things on it
it's just so like getting the content
structure the content types
and what content that we we want there
and also
how it's structured and the taxonomies
and stuff
and so it's easy to find things as well
you know so um
yeah so that's why i was thinking about
the book idea for the project
so i said if you're there you can just
click through and you can have a
directory of
project books and that will contain all
information
we can go and write your own story as i
said i'll use the forums for like
creating social media strategies and
strategies for what for each of your
projects and what you're doing
and it can get people just like you know
obviously
there's going to be outside people who
come in but so if we
were talking to yvette tomorrow so i
thought with me you and yvette get
together and i'd like to get together
with adriel matushen bentley
and then figured out you know principles
and everything else before joining
so we can work on the who and the why
and then we forget those straight and
then we can take it from there
and as i said it doesn't have to scale
off i'm not
interested in it scaling up to huge
amounts of people but i'm more
really interested in the relationships
that people have in there
with the projects and stuff and that
because that's the main
because the relationships with who into
the who that matters more than anything
else
um so yeah so um
yeah so that'd be great so it's for a
small number of people
so like maybe a few hundred at this
point and just
or like what number are you envisioning
at what point is this one not working
and we need a
bigger better oh well well i think about
jupiter do you want to turn your bike
off
um do you want to mute yourself jubilee
ah that's better right the thing about
drupal is that you
you can scale it scale it up to big
numbers of people
so i'm not saying that i want it to grow
huge and massive and all of that
but one also has a nucleus me all of us
seeing an event
as a nucleus crew kind of
um and as i said as we meet people and
as we get talking to them
and if they want to you know i mean they
don't have to but it's not mandatory
you know if they want to come along and
join and then but i just think it'd be a
good idea to see everybody's project
see where you're at and as i said if you
leave questions because we're all over
the place
it's difficult to know where to leave
messages
that don't get lost in in in everything
else you know i mean
so and if i see research that pertains
to adriel's project or bentley's or
matu's project or yours
you know i mean i could i can leave
stuff that you'll actually see
you know i mean and then we can take it
from there and help each other to like
develop strategies for
moving along and stuff so um
but as i said we'll be the kind of
nucleus of it
and then we'll kind of structure the
network so as people are joining
you know today for either the the people
who've got the projects have invited
them in
or it's somebody who's wanting to come
and join us and then that way
we can get to know so i've been watching
loads of stuff about community building
and it's it's the wider people go for
but it's the who that makes the people
stay
you know i mean so as i said if we
figured out the who and the principles
and that
and then because what i don't want is
people coming in and just deciding to be
total ourselves
um and then we'll go well what do we do
and we just you know
you need you need to sort of like sort
things out from the get-go
so they know if they've got these
principles to to at least abide by
then you know if the the ourselves
they're gone
you know what i mean because we
shouldn't have to put up with that and
he knew the rules anyway
so you know i mean what is the
definition of asshole gary
well someone paid a complete dick to
other people
for them no reason at all nothing that's
all
fair enough i mean i don't know how how
hard that
it's hard to know what that that line is
and um for me anyway i want to create a
culture
where people are allowed to make
mistakes i.e the assholes and redeem
themselves without necessarily needing
to you know be kicked out and do
in facebook that's nearly impossible and
i'm not saying something you're creating
is going to be able to
be able to facilitate but if we're doing
it from a small base um
and growing is there a way to because
what i'm seeing in other
like there's the game b that i admit and
then the kyle sees one that went by the
wayside
because all the other admins were
getting their feelings hurt of like this
person criticized me i'm so and it's
like
yeah they're it they like they were so
mean i'm like they mentioned
something and i'm not saying that that's
what's going to necessarily happen but
if it's like one person's
feels triggered then like what is the
metric for kicking someone out
but if you open it up to everyone there
will be trolls and there are people
trying to be assholes
trying to be an asshole versus trump
just being yourself
means an asshole and having a bad day
and being an asshole
to me it's different but that doesn't
mean that that's what it means
oh okay well i know there's going to be
people who are going to be on the edges
right and you can learn from people on
the edges and
like if someone's called you something
because you've been getting on the case
or whatever
i'm like well you shouldn't you know i
mean so take a
a view of the situation that's arise
straight
or even find out why they're acting like
that
right and what what reasons and i'm not
talking about oh you know i don't like
your hair
or whatever oh you you look a bit
scruffy
so you know i mean no i mean
constantly sort of like maybe
oh i don't know um i've yet to have yet
to meet
someone like even in communities and
that as i said if
we there's always going to be people on
the edges who don't count who kind of
skate by
and and they're going to sort of like
maybe not live up to the criteria
like you're allowed to be an asshole at
times but if you don't know soul all the
time
for no reason just got it you've got to
have a reason but as i said they'd find
out
and why they were being like that and
what what you know and and maybe give
them something to do
you know what i mean because a lot of
people who are trolls they're so
just bored and got nothing to do
so i'm sure if we find them something to
do and something that they're
they're contributing there's something
that they want
to do then then we can take it from
there but as i said i'm not
going you know like there's different
levels of meanness
that people like for someone could be
really mean to me and
i i might not see it or see it that way
but somebody else might
so but um as i said just find them
something to do
you know what i mean
if they want to yeah that would be a
good a good solution
so i'm just gonna one of the things this
is not a small group of people it's the
opposite of what i think you need
but to be able to block people
effectively
actually makes a community as opposed to
hurts it like if you if
i know that bentley and i can get and if
i don't want to hear from for a month i
can just mute him or i can block him
completely
then i don't need to worry about
everyone else also ostracizing him or
vice versa like it actually
helps because i can just be like we have
a personality conflict
we can't sit at the same table and make
sure we're not gonna sit at the same
table
versus me needing everyone to gang up on
him because he's a horrible human being
because he said something that hurt my
feelings and so
he's out of here or i'm out of here
which it's very different to be like oh
actually
we can just separate like we could just
never be at a meeting again
and it also gives the empowerment to be
like
or is there another option do we have a
conflict resolution thing like
is there but it's up to bentley and i in
this case right to decide
are we both in that or do we want to
have the resolution
and if we're neither of us one of us
doesn't want to
then blocking is the easiest way but
again
i don't think with 20 people you want
that it's more with like 200 people
well as i said yeah it could the stuff
that could be built in
as we go because as i said it'll just
i'm i'm hoping
well i think it will emerge
and i i i don't know which way it's
going to emerge but i'm just going to
let it because you can't plan for the
emergence because that's not emergence
is it
so i'm just going to start with us
see what you know because the aim is to
sort of like get everybody here
so you know i've sucked some success and
to develop some success
in what they're doing as well you know
what i mean so
and as the the community side of it
that's there to save you all you know i
mean
as as as best as i can and to
to make sure that you've got everything
that you need
and obviously if people come in and they
want to to like play out with us
you know i mean um and that's great
because
and we'll take it from there as i said
it's all about the who and if you're
enjoying
spending your time and having fun and
doing stuff
and it's working and you're getting
together and things are going along
and you've got a place to hang out that
you know you feel comfortable in
and that you know i mean so so i mean
i'm sorry karen
um i mean so the the what i thought you
were doing with the drupal site was kind
of like a resource for projects
so i didn't think of that as a as a
hangout space or a space where
personalities would have a big thing as
more information and maybe
like you said a place you can put things
but i mean it sounds like you're
saying something that would be an
alternative to the facebook page
well well it's well no it's not going to
be an alternative
as i said there's going to be a
directory listings and also
so it's like a place for research so so
belly so say if i'm coming across some
research for you in your project
i can put it in a place and we can
create documents or whatever
and that will be sort of like right
research for
reason score and all these links that
you can have
and things and make it kind of like a
media thing so whether it's images
whether it's videos whether it's you
know
stuff that you need to know and also on
the
and build social media strategies to
and leave it and that'll be specific to
yours
and then you love that there so if
anybody comes in and who's looking for
stuff
me he's looking at your project oh that
might help me in mine
you know what i mean so yeah right
so i guess what i'm saying is that the
the part about like
the people that's there drawing stuff
it's not a community thing so those
principles that you're bringing up
apply more to our facebook presence than
to
well it could be both you know you know
what i mean so
yeah so but i think those principles
don't apply that much in that space it's
not yeah
space yeah yeah until there's a lot of
capacity for people like to go and add
comments and
have the whole like chain that you get
in facebook
it might just end up being somebody you
know puts a resource like i think that
reason score would you know that this
resource is applicable and somehow i'm
posting that they also post something
insulting
i guess
i don't have any like expectations for
this new site or needs for it
right okay i mean it's even it's a bit
of a distraction
um but i'm willing to give it a try
because i mean right now
if anyone wants to learn about my
project or give me feedback i'd rather
that go through my web page
this resource might be good for people
that don't have that
yeah well well as i said you know the
projects listing
will be on the outside and now it's it's
you know i mean so there will be links
to your page and that
you know what i mean so anyone coming
across it the the link will be made
public
for everybody to see what the projects
are
and they can take it from that and
obviously if they wanna
or if they've got a project of their own
that they might wanna come and join
the back end of it you know i mean um
and stuff like that so it's definitely
uh your vision so far and
so i'd like to see you know you've told
us a bit about it but i'm not sure i can
like
picture it in my mind so maybe
when you get kind of the first version
you know
once those name servers were yeah we
could have a meeting and
you could show us what you got and we
could yeah i was just going to make a
sandbox
do what do i can and then get you to
come in
and have a polka down yeah i think it'd
still be helpful even
i mean a sandbox doesn't help if i don't
know what
what it was for so it's not like you
just have a meeting where you show us
what you were thinking
right okay because the sandbox would you
know i could do anything in there it's
like well what
what do i want to do i'd like a little
direct
okay okay i'll do that
that sounds like a good idea the other
thing i was thinking when you were
talking about you get like you
having research and then knowing like
where to put it when you see something i
know
um part of me worries that that gets
very what's the word busy
with um like on facebook feed right if i
would like i have friends who i know
if there's anything about chickens it's
going to get on this one friend's post
is there anything about crochet it's
going to get on this one but not because
they post it because everyone posted
right like
hey this is this is a um sense-making
thing so i gotta tell adriel and bentley
about it
so like i don't know what the tagging is
so that it's actually
like with a project what i would find
helpful would be the categories
of those like having like i don't want
any blog posts to be like oh this is
somewhat a little bit pertaining to your
to your stuff because one i don't like
homework and that feels like homework
but like if it's not explaining it to me
right like if it's not
if it's real research i want to know
about it if it's if it's something in
the same space i'm in that i don't know
about what i want to know about it but
how are you going to know right that
yeah
and so there's something about but
that's
not the tool you're creating but like
having
organized research right where it's like
as things come up has someone posted
already and how does it
get somewhere so that it can get to the
person who needs it
in a way that it's not just a news feed
right of like oh
there's 15 000 things that are saving
the world and i cannot possibly
read through all of them absolutely
pretend so what
yeah so like if someone's posting on my
projects page like oh i think this is
interesting
do i have the ability to de-emphasize
that or hide it or
um what i'll do is once it's set up i'll
give you you'll have access
to it so you can change you can update
it
you can if someone's left if you can
have the choice whether you want
comments on it or not
um you can have your contact details so
they can contact you
um but it's up to you it'll be up to you
because it's your project and you know
you can have what you want seen or not
seen and that
and as i said if you you may be thinking
about something
that you wanted to put that you didn't
want public
you could make it so that it wasn't in
the public realm
sort of thing so you'd have a choice
between sort of like out in the public
or kind of you know between whoever's in
the community space
i'm going to call it a co-creating space
sort of thing
you know um
[Music]
just so all right so i'll i'll show you
and then then you can see and then
as i said we can have a chat about
categories and stuff because i was going
to ask you about project categories
and what types of categories there are
that are out there because i noticed on
the knack site there wasn't
you couldn't tell what status a project
was at
so whether it was just the ideas the
planning the execution
they're already launched there was no
way of telling that
you know what i mean so um so yeah so
that's
but i'll do it and i'll show you
sounds good looking forward to playing
with it is there anything else we need
to
discuss outside of that i.e the facebook
page itself
or anything that would help anyone
else's project
that we can easily do that we're not
doing in the moment
right now i guess
with the facebook page so if you think
if you
do you think it'd be better if you
posted about the the live
is there any way you can put the live
what we're doing here
or maybe a few days earlier or something
i'm supposed to do it on sunday but it
hasn't been getting done on sunday
it got done yesterday not even 24 hours
beforehand
so yes it should be and i will try to
get it yes
get up earlier than that the things that
we wanted to mention
um kerry and bentley were there we had a
solution raising on voting with your
wallet with mark campbell
and so next week at this time we're
doing a
project raising for that same the same
concept
with mark so whoever wants to come to
that and help raise that
that project he'll give the parameters
and then we'll focus on creating that
are you going to be doing a project
raising first solutions raising them
no because you and me and vet are going
to basically do that right over the
course of a couple weeks we're kind of
doing a
prolonged one unless that's changed and
then maybe maybe
we'll see what comes out of our
conversation tomorrow
my hair doesn't want to do it i want to
do anyone else's thoughts on this
so yeah i guess um
is there any other together tech
game b projects business we wanted to
chat about
nothing i can think of i think like
there's a lot of things that branch off
of
the project that carrie is working on
but i think until we see it
i was sure where to go with it and sort
of
where to take that there has been more
people registering for an act recently
which i didn't expect
on the nation like the
trying to get access to like as a member
to the together tech
part of neck how many people
um look over the last two weeks maybe
eight
do the names look like people on the
facebook group or do you think it's just
i haven't been
comparing it because i'm wondering
i mean i think i did post it in the
introduction
for the game b group okay so that may be
where they're getting it or we may just
be getting bots and stuff
right that sounds possible but like they
there's one question asking like how did
you hear about us and they seemed like
real
like real answers which i guess i think
some of them did say
that you know the the game b at the
facebook page and
one that i just finally got around to
activating today said like a web search
which that one theoretically could be
fake because i'm not really sure how
you'd find it through web search but
then you have found together tech
through a web search and then
like a few weeks ago i googled solution
raising and
i was all that came up because it's
there isn't anything else that
comes up with solution raising now when
i look it up
both on twitter unless i hashtag it with
it together then i show up but otherwise
raising solutions shows up before
solution raising
even in quotation marks and i was all
that showed up it was all my facebook
all youtube all everything and i'm just
like that is weird that that's no longer
happening but
whatever that there was something else
to do with that
you're muted
sorry so we wouldn't know if anyone was
just going on the knack site and putting
a whole bunch of
links to their own stuff and
i'm just thinking we may need to
we'll have to make a decision at some
point to shut down knack if
we want to go with what carries done
yeah yeah i think at a certain point
yeah because i also haven't been
maintaining it all that much because i
could currently still need somebody to
go in there and manually improve
the user accounts which i haven't been
great at doing because i didn't really
think that we were using it and then i
started to get some registrations but
you say this is like a cool agile
project on a whole other level of like
bring people together with projects
figure out
like that we get a sandbox to play in
and see if it can be something that is
created
around us and because there's enough us
enough projects
it might actually turn into something
powerful that other people want to come
and be part of
and which is different it's different
than what we were doing
like what's the bare minimum we can do
alongside well i guess we have to like i
think this is harry's
important stuff which is different and
cool but like it's not like i've had
someone make me a
web page for free and awesome but
they can't maintain it and i can't
maintain it this is like uh
agile it will grow around us and with us
i guess so i forgot i also
took over the game b wiki page and just
put a link to
our knack site so anyone
gave me projects wiki
did um you talk to the people at the
wiki page in terms of what
we could put on there or what or
managing it or what yeah i mean first of
all you don't need to ask because it's a
wiki
second of all yes i did ask and they
basically said sounds good
so i went and made the changes and i
said hey i made the changes i said
okay it didn't seem to mind that i wiped
out everything they had before i mean a
link to it just buried it further but
well are you wanting any other stuff put
on there then
i'd well i would rather not have
duplicate places we have to update
things so if we're going to put it right
okay
so what i think we'll do is once we get
comfortable with your site we'll remove
the knack site and put
that entire site there and then if we
want to
yeah i would not want to have two places
we have to update so we'd have to figure
out
it'd be neat if we ever need to like if
we want to expose stuff out there more
to find some way to auto populate it or
something
right because i know media wiki is part
of the
the drupal module it's one of them
the the wiki that the game has a
wikipedia
yeah but media wiki um what the
the game b wiki's on that's that's the
kind of plug-in from
a module that comes with drupal so you
could attach
you could attach it or whatever they
call it well i
i think drupal has okay yeah they might
have a
integration point yeah i wouldn't know
about that integrate that's the word
integration thing
right yeah
so it'd be nice on that first page to
say you don't have our
first page on that page too and then
when they click in
it takes them to our thing and you get
more abilities that'd be nice at some
point
but yeah let's see how it goes
oh and also would you want um i'm not
sure you can do
feeds from groups into a main space
um i'm not sure you'd want that anyway
but that's that's a possibility but
i'm i think i was because i'm part of
this um
social media marketing group for
facebook
and that and um it's been interesting
following them
um and seeing what they do but i know
they were saying they have
pages and groups is there a game b
project page as well
on the wiki well no just in facebook
you know we are the i mean not a page no
we just have the game b
projects group right because i was
thinking if this
because a lot of people get um traction
from
the page right so you could choose your
page
to have certain specific items on
that would lead to maybe if they're
interested in that coming to join the
group
or whatever yeah that's usually helpful
when you have a public page in a private
group
right since we have a public group i
think we show up in the search is the
same as if we had a public page
okay i could be wrong on that though
okay okay
questions so many game b
groups that like them duplicating and
having game b
pages as well is like a whole other
level of too much too much but
i do that yeah i might get your help do
that for solution raising i have a page
in a group
any other interesting news that people
want to talk about
that's kind of game b ish
i think at some point you me and maybe
matush and who
whoever else can connect about the org
tracker that we talked about using
the prototype for wiki election slash
conferrati and seeing how those sort of
overlap
so yeah also on this meeting next week
when we talk about the um
the with your wallet
that i'm thinking the same base
technology would be used for
first of all that does overlap with with
the
company's one yeah the politicians one
would be slightly different
um but i think it would be the same base
tech so yeah i'm hoping to build the
base tech
um and i don't know if you all saw the
um the google
doc i shared on the tuesday thing so in
there i put in my ideas including my
suggested technology
for it i'm thinking about going with
mongodb instead of firebase
so that's a little bit more cloud
agnostic and turns out mongodb now has
cloud functions and it's not called
mongo it's their bigger thing
but cloud functions and uh
authentication so it's kind of like
the open source version of firebase
so so where did you say that you put
that
google talk uh on the thursday
i guess it was the thursday
um well like it was in a comment on
maybe it was
the live stream yeah was is the comment
on the uh
what have you done you're uh oh okay
cool yeah yeah
i was thinking about making a bigger
post but since we're kind of
following mark's project
i wanted to let that be the driving
force but
we'll keep in mind in the conversation
that we also want to do that and then i
have a no code
solution um finder and
community rating system that i want to
use it for too so
see if we can get all that stuff
together in one
core project
that can then be reused
might have enough people to actually
enough interest to
you know get more than two people on
something for once right
yeah i'll catch up with this on uh well
this weekend
because uh for the past few days i was
badly distracted with
uh just amazing amount of
things so i did notice
the ideas and
your post as well about it
so yeah i'll catch up uh tomorrow most
probably
and uh yeah yeah and we'll talk more
about it doesn't it
i'll just a reminder tomorrow is our
first round table that's five hours
later
at 2pm instead of 9am it is posted at
the correct time on youtube and facebook
but if you didn't see that
so if you're all up and ready at the
same time 9am we're kind of meeting at
10am
what's up
so has anyone actually um
asked for the later time and
specifically
that is a good question we'll see we'll
see if anyone joins i did
ask the group i said if it's at 2 pm who
will watch it
who will and there was enough people and
there was some i know there are
australians and new zealanders who are
like jonas might be there i don't know
like
this just is not at the right time for
them oh this one is actually sorry
there's not this one the 9am one is like
but but no one made um has made a
commitment of any sort
okay so if after i'd say two weeks no
one shows up i mean it's the five of us
a lot
like anyway so why move it to 2 p.m and
9 a.m if we're the only ones coming
but it might be different people
watching at 2pm and we might get
yeah i guess at 2pm is it do we just in
general hit more people in the world
i guess so maybe quite possibly it's
like late in europe but not super late
and early in australia but not
super early i think that's just
and it works for north america we all
know the world centers around
the universe i think right that's right
san francisco specifically
maybe washington canada is pretty
we like to be there like the entourage
okay well maybe we can go ahead and end
early if yeah
we all have our own projects we're
working on
sounds good all right and broadcast
thanks together tech